Guide to the John Watts Papers, 1945-1982 MSS.093
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries A: Watts - Works on Tape
    - Encounter Out takes Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_104b31e0a4f2f91a1873757a80a11fbd)
    - Locrian Note: Matrix Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_7b119348962be86e2e0aa3df74480fd8)
    - Locrian Note: Extra material, eerie track II Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_43c3471334152838b0ef060ee736b383)
    - Locrian Note: 3 tapes various materials Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_c0abe85fc26184fea4c81e72800939a4)
    - Faust Note: Opening March Format: 1/2", undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_8bbd9d809a663191a0c238cd2d2fcd3b)
    - Faust Note: Opening Wind tracks Format: 1/2", undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_d3225cdd26d1ad4f54ddc09544ebdbec)
    - Faust Note: Curtain Call Format: 1/2", undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_8ee8696523d34381043f85785d7fb5d5)
    - Faust Note: Final Tolling, Whistles, Katrina Dear Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_3da982e7a471af1804bdf1072a97a416)
    - Faust Note: Opening Act II, Fun Thing steel drum Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_d0d7089cfaddb10f89ac3afbbb028113)
    - Faust Note: End of Act I, Hurdy Gurdy Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_53949b7f482473d3b018648fa20a7b78)
    - Faust Note: Chimes, Filters, Perky, Knocking Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_41b8e96f029221699c7ff19dd9f52312)
    - Faust Note: Organ Point Material Act I Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_475a41de926abb84d7b012216ec220a7)
    - Faust Note: Two excerpts from off-Bway prod. of Faust 1973 Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_a71158678fb493d0739b39c7c1087fb3)
    - Faust Note: Thunder Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_1cbef47de200cca10a98e5ba97919424)
    - Faust Note: Thunder, wind music Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_475ad1dffa48ea1c1992227b4795b33a)
    - Faust Note: opening mixdown Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_daf9457d87de59b1cdae7b83c9711de1)
    - Faust Note: Beware of love bits Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_ca2cc796622561b2b2dfe6f6b0e0b276)
    - Faust Note: Mephistopheles shouts with thunder A & B Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_10382b63b53adc08caeee48b22591795)
    - Faust Note: Hurdy Gurdy for Curtain calls Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_23a96b9dc1b94c168285a133feaa7133)
    - Faust Note: Fragment from Intro - devils Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_e0f90d06612a7cd8d5b1958daca9c0a8)
    - Faust Note: Basic Opening tracks I & II Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_e3fb5cfcbe2fbbf7d17949a82565bdcc)
    - Faust Note: Maledicat Dominus organ point Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_dccff0a4a77e72771ce43f8d3a5d546b)
    - Faust Note: Leftovers Knock B part of mischief Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_288fb5020c1572d691a08d4e08b5f2af)
    - Faust Note: Elements Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_2e563266ffb91582bb3dbdb2ae66f50f)
    - Faust Note: Leftovers - raw voices Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_20737c283f65cbe488fd02a328792844)
    - Laura's Dance, Postludes Note: Basic tracks Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_eaa14d5e3212874cc567b9141ac9028e)
    - Laura's Dance Note: 4 Channel Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_f596937613759ef35afe26a5214d74c7)
    - Laura's Dance Note: 7 tapes - various versions Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_76af0a7a3142984a426fe5a789aabd77)
    - Fugue for Two Pf's, Two Pieces for Flute Note: Boulder concert Brand: Audiotape Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_3d354d9460f6f684fe68d71b896dc0fe)
    - Film Note: splices Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_c47810eccb51520685e7a6933690ee99)
    - Jeff's Cues Note: II Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_311112a819177e3f3e8262cfb48b3eac)
    - Jeff's Cues Note: II Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_c98cadd9e7d86606e44a3d588992d53d)
    - Jeff's Cues Note: Master Mixes 15ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_aec017199e55ee0892ccbad3e27d588b)
    - Jeff's Cues Note: Mixdowns Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_2143116586072d2876071d4e8c654929)
    - Gallery Piece Note: Re-dub from Master Format: 1/2", undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_e56b3d58ddfa44ac76a89cf414c8677f)
    - Gallery Piece Note: Noise patch - use re-dub Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_16c8ac27799f41170010e7b74ce659c7)
    - Gallery Piece Note: Quad, background Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_f3eb94bfbf3de2db734f47f4aaefe8ea)
    - Gallery Piece Note: Quad, background Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_17427a304e93008cc7151ac5ad05bc81)
    - Glass & Shadows Note: Agfa Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_46c264652a1a135cdd5cd1f4f2e0a4ce)
    - Gallery Piece Note: 3 tapes various backgrounds Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_47eaf0b5acc16235f353f34f2bf79956)
    - Gallery Piece Note: 1977 concert demo tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_c99f9007d1d51d1c8832d0d9bbeac4ca)
    - Glass & Shadows Note: 8 tapes various versions Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_ddfe558d5ff1b0114721ff4540acdb8c)
    - Glass & Shadows Note: New version 1975, rehearsal Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_5aac7848d40ed39a935945e499d3bea0)
    - Glass & Shadows Note: Intro, Moulin Rouge Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_5d93ab61dce33910df5c45f72fc81acc)
    - Glass & Shadows Note: ATL concerts 1971 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_e71c09604af7fc8b10f04e6470ec8d27)
    - Glass & Shadows Note: Master tape - reward if found Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_98fe6f85e75411ef91453fea97002838)
    - Glass & Shadows Note: 1973 MOMA copy, reward Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_7c093e3fc618de814abb429d808376f5)
    - Heirlooms Note: C mixes Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_1181870d5ddb908bd522bc5045aa8280)
    - Heirlooms Note: B mixes Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_b764202aebb28d475a00dbcc18fd0738)
    - Introix Note: Mixes, use #3 for dubs Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_4252cbe80366f2a0493d399e02697abc)
    - Introix Note: Master, 4 tracks Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_46ce7255b4bba1519965d764a14570cd)
    - Heirlooms Note: Lincoln Center NYCB Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_feb51db195660e820b127020d3802b72)
    - Heirlooms Note: 5 tapes Basic tracks Quad Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_f7308a719bb1973bc2756dbe512e7ba4)
    - Heirlooms Note: "Section I Concerto, undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_821e5bda198bc8780bbe52a03651d3f2)
    - Sec. II Rondo (Stereo mix)" Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_7a8ae1c1a7f353f34f24e3d04c3d40f0)
    - Heirlooms Note: Section III Dirge 1/4 track stereo mix Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_a3e10a238fb861b5e0d4a4f2d5b89adc)
    - Heirlooms Note: 5 tapes Stereo mixes of various elements Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_a4bf715e4090e666df3c34949babb6af)
    - Heirlooms Note: 5 tapes Mono, stereo, quad various mixes" Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_1c610b82acdf40c95d9bc636a8acef96)
    - Introix Note: Two channel version 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_c3a14173d2145d72c93c75ea3d74b9fc)
    - Introix Note: Master two-channel 15 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_5404afba6b37e3172659d15a4095ad5e)
    - Introix Note: Tape I, Ch. 1& 2, 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_7978cc498c1b9b99d13a0da7116488e6)
    - Introix Note: Tape II, Ch. 3 & 4, 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_4a35b0d6285c04bcb502ab780a674875)
    - Introix Note: Dub of master, 7.5 ips half-track has hum Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_b1d80dfc75643901f21be08957f17163)
    - Keepsakes Note: Take 5 Orch only + tape background, Trial Studio Mix Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_9ab7212b1aa27a69ccaba484f5753b52)
    - Keepsakes Note: Bennington Takes 3 & 4 compl. Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_00e3eb5cc090d58e504cf685b58a9687)
    - Keepsakes Note: Bennington Takes 5 & 6 orch only + tape Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_e8b63592eba0d4d91122530962c69195)
    - Keepsakes Note: Bennington Takes 1 & 2 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_600459574ce7783bff46990e3932b5aa)
    - Keepsakes Note: Studio version Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_fb355e1eb30e1a46c8029fc4ee20b31d)
    - Keepsakes Note: Benington Mix Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_5841c60cbba65b11de1cbae6e7a189fe)
    - Keepsakes Note: Orch piece Track 1 & II Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_4a3ce618907569f7381fb8359707a94b)
    - Keepsakes Note: Sage City Symphony, Bennington, VT 1980 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_20b795d9f66b4e93240a5fc66a1a4f03)
    - Keepsakes Note: O'Neal/Bennington; Takes 3 & 4 complete Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_64b6afc63b575510b2c6ac676455346e)
    - Keepsakes Note: O'Neal/Bennington; Takes 1 & 2 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_cd320a57cade924ec05b9e9cd4b84fe5)
    - Keepsakes Note: O'Neal/Bennington Takes 5 & 6 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_80dad256e8e7b58831e45b0b4a750963)
    - Keepsakes Note: Tape Background Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_5550e8fc075a3026dde43af74dfb16f9)
    - Keepsakes Note: JH Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_8694c0f658b983d384a3609f04f235c0)
    - Keepsakes Note: original - flaws in ch 1 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_a880c1bde4bd0e0f439c4a7bd495ddb1)
    - Keepsakes Note: so-so copy Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_f6cc28fa9865e1bb437d1ad8cbe9d60a)
    - Keepsakes Note: demo tape rec. 1978 premiere 2-channel mono Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_0c5b230022d937c4981be1f4b59b2864)
    - Keepsakes, UPS, Mas Note: 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_2c78d07c5484c0cf841c3f58a6ed2434)
    - Killers Program Note: Dub of program Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_988524ff2f40dbe5ef6633a55719b722)
    - Laugharne Note: Work tape Format: 1/2", undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_e3f9d888140cd540450772c807a189cd)
    - Laugharne Note: Master tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_c20162f6f645f448135e05ac4e915e81)
    - Laugharne Note: Composers Festival Orch part 3, 1977 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_289e9deb79864f3ad7e43f9f63ac1cea)
    - Laugharne Note: Background tape Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_f36a298894e0ee8c986c23f03a5032a1)
    - Laugharne Note: Use as master for dubs Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_8c563f92b9e0f2a987857aab65dbc885)
    - Laugharne Note: Quad, Nuits - 2 passes Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_050620922475c2c8c15efe33c5fad986)
    - Laugharne Note: Background tape for perf. Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_b9e665901ec676c228755448046bc35d)
    - Laugharne Note: Demo tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_f467f179b2a7e888cfe7221bfd6fd559)
    - Laugharne Note: Background tape 15 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_d46ba705f0bafdfa99c4ad0fded00307)
    - Laugharne Note: Background tape, 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_21a4632a02444a6f6533d8d334208601)
    - Laugharne, Elegy to Chimney Note: Demo tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_71142f97f264956a2cf512d5015813bf)
    - Laugharne Note: 8 track tape Brand: no box Format: 1-inch, undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_bbccf9079862b276bf034c721d656161)
    - Maxiconcerto Note: boos at end Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_39c58e4fd76d0bbaa89a51ebffb9f2fc)
    - Mas Note: 1976 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2" (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_9e6b8e73dc755b8244c1542ef73e7e24)
    - Mas Note: Demo - "Mas for Tape" realized on ARP Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_95446fe3a3d841806e18e392894228f2)
    - Mas Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_36bccfc0ec401a05faffea6fac79fcb5)
    - Mas Note: for dubs, NAB 15ips, 4-tk Brand: Ampex Format: 1/4", undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_df81aa2df04a61b7c5aee46dc15ac5d7)
    - Memorials Note: Dance score for Piano + ens. Rehearsal 1966 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_29f075168e8919c751f2c6c4c28cb5b4)
    - Memorials Note: Master Tape 15ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_478efe78f70d6990cd36639ebf74c6d1)
    - Memorials Note: Master copy Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_f590ad1e0d2c1a571ad0f3336992b31f)
    - Memorials Note: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_9225c834f72f3570aa82660af06b0fa9)
    - Memorials Note: Score for dance Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_ad770ba7d8dd35c29a0637866b7d277e)
    - Optional (Roses) Note: 15ips, 4-channel Format: 1/2", undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_08432e6e49b9293b7ee3ba28c9ffae70)
    - Pastorale for Strings and Horns Note: mono Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_64b1e4801fe1950b37d7068f6988d389)
    - Performance [cubiculo?] Note: 4-TK, 15ips Format: 1/2", undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_f67b49a852e8dae3144cca7e567dafdc)
    - Performance Note: Audience Tracks Format: 1/2", undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_3c973c1566ed579c071a621bead4ff2c)
    - Performance Note: Dub for use in concert, music tape Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_0e57af805297ea721c9966ea8cce023a)
    - Performance Note: Two mixes Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_6f5b7a4bb541ba0bb2d2930b207ba97a)
    - Perimeters Note: two-track Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_1f6d2a78728a07f154f9aabe5e460129)
    - Perimeters Note: stereo, from epicycles Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_cb669ce6ab1c139378857542996d805c)
    - Perimeters Note: mono, complete, other things on 2nd tk Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_d753612296434552b1d27359e4bc6992)
    - Perimeters Note: Tape construction for Dance 1969, mono Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_0b09332658881eaf93b434a10e46e5af)
    - Phillips No. 1 Note: inserts for master Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_feb133936860ee1de8ff5aa516153b2a)
    - Phillips No. 1 Note: III-IV Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_dc73a164955b827ee8e255c4f656db02)
    - Phillips No. 2 Note: I & II, master version Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 50, Folder data_value_missing_03e75441cb34a48a95ae2ea929fe09d3)
    - Piano For te Note: Dub, pf background Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_ed640faa50523d4b3bb3a3f6cdac8fba)
    - Piano For te Note: pf background Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_d3c39b399e158b062e40741fbadc1c5d)
    - Piano For Te Note: Background tape, 15ips, 4-channels Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_377b7fa8a173a1f384ad42760899fa1a)
    - Piano For te Note: 4 ch. 15ips Mix I, concert version Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_9929e4752d3db5b23d9fb89719c1b000)
    - Piano For te Note: Mix II 15ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_73be55da92470c47b6ba38a32c7e4f54)
    - Piano For te Note: Tracks (16 tracks) Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_adb2d3396b94bd14f4cd0eb1af472e75)
    - Piano For te Note: 4 ch, 15ips 1973 [for perf.] Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2" (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_67ae352ff3cfac0c53af4e853f680e7a)
    - Piano For te Note: 15ips, quad Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_519fd0921d7d35ded1c379e2a4e18c23)
    - Piano For te Note: 7.5 ips, background Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_6f37670c27850cb5e1544d84f404ad76)
    - Piano For te Note: 7.5 ips, background tape, half-track stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_f73576f6a553883bee6eec6fca217a39)
    - Piano For te Note: 7.5 ips, quad, backgrnd tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 51, Folder data_value_missing_71d0e8ae2dd724430051d6f63608daab)
    - Piano For te Note: 15ips, 4-channel, quad Brand: Agfa Format: 1/4", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_11e19eb487692b80d3c7204a0b944e1d)
    - Piano For te Note: 15ips, 4-channel, backgrnd Brand: Agfa Format: 1/4", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_4a2b59d802e7afb31c109284f789edd4)
    - Piano For te Note: Brass Background, Gongs [copy of the score is inside the tape box] Brand: Agfa Format: 1/4", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_f35e6c2f0d7415ef1482a0f8d85f31d3)
    - Piano For te Note: background dub, abrupt at end, good dub Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_e1bb39bdf526db024c542c19c34e386f)
    - Piano For te Tutti Note: Piano and tape String, Gongs, New School perf. Track Brand: RCA Format: 1/2", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_1c549b43617ecb356c1f906ba1d5bc44)
    - Piano For te Tutti Note: Reconstituted Dub, 15 Format: 1/2", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_31d6ecc1951ef16acde4dccc926f80d2)
    - Piano For te Tutti Note: for performance, backgrnd 4-ch, 15ips Format: 1/2", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_4654bbced71e87514b78eae5aa6537ce)
    - Piano For te Tutti Note: Backgrnd master for dubs,15 ips Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 52)
    - Piano For te Tutti; Mother Goose [Donnez], and Audience Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_fa14e50b4ec612c71998c3602aa90436)
    - Piano for te Tutti Note: Warren's Ur-mix Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_966810085d2c54f1ef99b265fcefda7d)
    - Piano for te Tutti Note: background tape, 7.5 ips, half-track stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_a1ec430d443b97764bbb50f276952868)
    - Quartet for Tape Note: Wind, Tolling (footsteps), finale, Organ point; MSS-Quartet for Tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 52, Folder data_value_missing_b96566a1fd9702dd0c15ab2cc6ada441)
    - Processional Note: Florida State Performance, use as master Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_f225dc6ec457ad845c52cbf8bf167421)
    - Processional Note: FSU - 4 takes Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_eb0d678ce74a5b6871cfd25fda90c517)
    - Processional Note: 3 complete takes 15ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_bc3453965c2e13b2bcd4b4ef85af0f6f)
    - Processional Note: Master Mix Brand: Ampex Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_3cb2524609ddb410c7816d5afeaba7b7)
    - Processional Note: Background tape, F Tuning note 7.5 stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_bdebd60949952e619fc2c1ea3effa572)
    - Processional Note: Tallahassee Trumpet Guild, perf. at Madison, WI, ITG convention, 1978 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_20cdbe82bd8fa679c5ee9cf9b8f9698a)
    - Processional Note: Tuning note, background tape 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_485615b6495d5cbf8d0ac52d342275ff)
    - Processional Note: Oberlin Performance Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_22f51ab62886a7e067ad4f72bd57d462)
    - Satoru's Piece Note: Work Tape, mixed at Hank's Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_0f1dacf37d600df33091df7e87fb2b0f)
    - Satoru's Piece Note: Master Work tape, Feb. 1978 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2" (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_fd3b30ea8058e07f492d136064f1caac)
    - Satoru's Dance Note: Four Basic tracks, pre-master 7.5, 1978 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2" (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_dabe483a286131356dc4de03f97d45ed)
    - Satoru's Dance Note: Mix for dubs Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_fcb27a20b673c7d9adf6a8b4442cd449)
    - Satoru's Piece Note: Mix of first four channels, Mix of first seven channels Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_0ea07cfda1518450440b23d369de56e5)
    - Satoru's Dance Note: Basic Material Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_2762d997a44d79a3fbe3e95a9420371d)
    - Satoru's Dance Note: Ur-master mix 7.5 ips Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_561422b24959030175f64152238e2176)
    - Signals Note: (Dance) 7.5 ips Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_9bf93d4e383e442b8049e3d2f23dd172)
    - Signals Note: Warning, new version 15ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_7fa0fa0ae2a0f9344c2784aaf9fd10e8)
    - Signals, Four Pieces, undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_e61e33f0f0f13f9de9cb5d0d0fc19918)
    - for Sat. Afternoon Note: 4-May-72 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_f8afdc97ec836658f70423f20e452bcf)